cricfeeds.com 2014-06-20

# Cricfeeds, B2B Cricket Service, Privacy Policy - Cricfeeds

**Privacy Policy**

Cricfeeds Team recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of information we may collect from our visitors. This privacy policy discloses how we collect, protect, use and share information gathered about you on our Web Site. We hope that this disclosure will help increase your confidence in this web site. Privacy issues are a high priority for us at Cricfeeds and we follow standard industry practices to maintain your personal information. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.  
**Cricfeeds does not spam or sell/lease its user information to third parties.**

**  Information Collection and Use**

We respect each visitor’s right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our web site only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to the information collected on Cricfeeds.com. Cricfeeds.com collects personal information when you register with the web site. This information consists of just your name and email address. The information we collect is:

  * Used to notify visitors about events, changes and other information about this web site.
  * Never shared with other organizations for commercial or other purposes.

**  Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

Cricfeeds.com will NOT disclose any personal information except in the following cases,

  * When required by law that such action is necessary.
  * Protect and defend the rights of property of Cricfeeds.com.

**Link to Other Sites :**

As a means of providing useful resources to our users, Cricfeeds.com provides links to other web sites. We try to carefully choose web sites that we believe are useful and meet our high standards. However, because web sites can change so quickly, we do not guarantee the standards of any website links we provide nor do we imply endorsement. Cricfeeds.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. Cricfeeds.com does not share any of the individual personal information that you provide with the sites to which Cricfeeds.com links, although we may share traffic data with such web sites such as how many people visit our site.

**  Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy.

**Access to your account information**

You can access and change the information that you provided during registration. Simply click on this link http://www.cricfeeds.com and then log in with your member name and password. You can access your personal information by clicking on “Change Profile” link after logging in. There are instructions on the start page to help you recover your password if you’ve forgotten it. You can also contact us via e-mail by clicking “Contact Us” in the top header bar of Cricfeeds.com page, or send an email directly to contactus@Cricfeeds.com. Please include information in the e-mail that will help us identify your account so we can assist you with your inquiry or request.

**  Copyrights**

**Copyrighted Material:** Uploading copies of copyrighted material as a whole or in part on Cricfeeds.com without explicit permission from the copyright owner shall be deemed to infringe on the copyright and this applies to materials such as text, images, music, movies, games, and other software in digital and analog format. Cricfeeds.com reserves the right to immediately delete such material without prior permission/consultation from the member. If you suspect that an image submitted to Cricfeeds.com is copyright protected and has been used fraudulently, please contact us immediately or send us an email to: member relations

**Contact Us**

If you need further assistance, please send us an email with your questions or comments to contactus@Cricfeeds.com or feel free to contact us at any time through this web site or at Privacy Matters, c/o Netzeta, Inc, 12816 Quail Creek Drive, Pearland, Texas 77584.
